everestaffiliates.com 2011-06-30

# Everest Affiliates

You can rest assured that Everest Affiliates will keep your information and promotional activity absolutely private. As a demonstration of our commitment to protecting partner privacy, we have adopted the following guidelines for our website as well as for the services we provide.

**Collection and Use of Information:**  We collect, retain and use information about you only for the purposes of providing requested services, as well as superior promotional opportunities to you. Information you provide is required in order for us to establish a viable working relationship.

**Keeping Information Private:**  We do not distribute personal information. We do not license, sell, rent or trade any personal information, including contact data or specific information about your accounts or other personally identifiable information, to any third party or to any other partners.

On occasion we contract with other companies to perform business services on our behalf. Some examples of these business services include sending email and postal mail, analyzing data, promotions fulfillment and processing payments. These companies may have limited access to personal information that is needed to perform contracted services, but they are prohibited from using it for any other purposes.

**Non-Personal Information:**  For research or promotional purposes, we may use non-personal, non-specific information to generate statistics on general partner activity, including player acquisition growth, overall earnings, payout amounts and promotional preferences, but these initiatives will never include any personally identifiable information without authorized partner consent.

**Protection of Information:**  We have implemented a number of security measures to safeguard your information. It is protected on secure networks and is accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. When you access areas containing your personal partner information, we use a secure server connection. Industry-standard encryption technologies are used when transferring or receiving sensitive information supplied by you. We update and test our technology on a regular basis to improve the protection of your information and to ensure the integrity of our systems.
